'use strict';

const STORE = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: 'Which band formed first?',
        option1: 'S.E.S.',
        option2: 'H.O.T.',
        option3: 'Finkl',
        option4: 'Shinhwa',
        answer: 'H.O.T.' 
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "What is Blackpink's Lisa's nationality?",
        option1: 'Chinese',
        option2: 'Korean',
        option3: 'Thai',
        option4: 'Japanese',
        answer: 'Thai'
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: 'Which of these is not a member of 2ne1?',
        option1: 'Tifanny',
        option2: 'Dara',
        option3: 'Park Bom',
        option4: 'CL',
        answer: 'Tifanny'
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: 'Which of these is not a song by S.E.S.?',
        option1: 'Dreams Come True',
        option2: "I Can't Cry",
        option3: 'Oh, My Love',
        option4: "I'm Your Girl",
        answer: "I Can't Cry"
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: 'Which movie did Taeyang see Min Hyo-rin in and requested her to be in his music video for 1am?',
        option1: 'Sunny',
        option2: 'Age of Milk',
        option3: 'The Grand Heist',
        option4: 'Twenty',
        answer: 'Sunny'
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: 'Which band made their US TV debut at the 2017 American Music Award?',
        option1: 'Seventeen',
        option2: 'Bigbang',
        option3: 'iKON',
        option4: 'BTS',
        answer: 'BTS'
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: 'Who is Kwon Ji-young?',
        option1: 'G-dragon',
        option2: 'Jay Park',
        option3: 'Tablo',
        option4: 'J-Hope',
        answer: 'G-dragon'
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: 'Which rapper was banned from entering South Korea?',
        option1: 'Yoo Seung-jun',
        option2: 'Jay Park',
        option3: 'Tablo',
        option4: 'MC Sniper',
        answer: 'Yoo Seung-jun'
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: 'Which K-pop music video was the first to reach 1 million views on Youtube?',
        option1: 'BIGBANG - Bae Bae',
        option2: "Girls' Generation - Gee",
        option3: 'PSY - Gangnam Style',
        option4: 'BTS- DNA',
        answer: 'PSY - Gangnam Style'
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: 'What is Gangnam?',
        option1: 'A dance move',
        option2: 'Older brother',
        option3: 'A rich district in South Korea',
        option4: 'A Korean cafe',
        answer: 'A rich district in South Korea'
    }
]